[ Watch on kissFlix.co ]
Ms. Nishino,
we've arrived at the hospital.
Releasing the lock.
-Lock's clear. Coming out.
-Copy.
Stretcher's down.
You're okay. We're at the hospital.
I'm gonna check you out.
-Room seven.
-We're moving.
Copy. Female, twenties,
fell down the stairs.
BP, 88 over 54. HR, 118.
Abdominal distension,
diaphoresis, facial pallor.
Condition at the time of the call?
She reported abdominal pain,
then fell down the stairs.
-Hurry.
-Right.
We talked to her family. Seems like
she's had stomach pain for a while.
-Been managing it with OTC meds.
-The swelling's pretty bad.
Okay, I'm putting a mask on you.
Give me some nice, slow breaths.
Anesthesia's going in now.
You'll start feeling a little sleepy.
Hm?
She's had work done.
What are all these people
trying to become anyway?
She had her jaw shaved
and her hooked nose fixed.
Plus a philtrum reduction
and, unsurprisingly,
she went for the M-shaped lips.
Now take a look.
See? It doesn't transfer at all.
Isn't this lipstick seriously great?
That's right. I'm glad you noticed.
I changed my nails too!
I tried natural blush this time.
Don't you think they look pretty?
Feel free to try it as well.
Guys, that's all for today!
Bye-bye!
Someone's livestream views
haven't been growing lately.
No need to be mean about it.
I already know.
You took on too many brand deals, boss.
Well yeah, for influencers,
it's all about brand deals.
You wanted to be
on the Girls Collection, right?
-I made it?
-Ta-da!
Oh, wow, this is huge!
-Yes! Let's go, let's go, let's go!
-This is insane!
Removing the drape.
Go ahead.
Her breasts.
They have both fat injections
and small-incision implants.
The surgical scars
are virtually invisible.
It's the perfect crime.
"Your beautiful body, my lady,
is a one-of-a-kind jewel
given to you by God."
"How tragic it would be
if you were to damage it
with your own two hands."
"It's all right, Elena."
"Only
by seriously hurting myself like this,
by going through pain and suffering,
will I get what I want."
Listen.
Just hitting your lines
with good enunciation isn't gonna cut it.
You have to be the character.
Understand what they're feeling,
and what the intention behind the line is.
Ms. Tanaka was the only one
whose intention came across.
Ms. Tanaka, good work.
-Thank you so much.
-Mm.
Okay, let's start from the top.
Ms. Tanaka, you're auditioning too?
Yes. I made it in time, right?
Uh, well, yes, I guess…
She's gonna kill it, you'll see!
You're on a whole other level.
Your acting isn't the problem, obviously.
-You're good, but…
-But what?
Honestly, this audition
will be decided by looks.
After all, they want someone
to partner with Kotomi Hiiragi.
GET CAST AS THE SISTER
OF KOTOMI HIIRAGI
Ah, Ms. Tanaka, you're skilled.
I just don't want you to be disappointed.
Yeah.
There'll be others.
-Sorry.
-Uh-uh. Let's go.
THE NASTASSIA OF PURITY
Making incisions all over
your body and pumping it full of drugs.
This isn't medicine.
It's an invasion.
An invasion of the human body.
Why is this allowed?
MOM: PLEASE CALL ME BACK
I NEED TO DISCUSS SOMETHING
ARE YOU OKAY? GET BACK TO ME
-Hey!
-Oh, sorry.
Are you struggling with something?
Your new self begins
right here.
Turn that dream into reality.
You can be reborn.
The Hand of God
will change you
for the better.
Are you truly happy
with who you are right now?
Everyone…
…can be beautiful if they want to.
Tohyama Cosmetic Surgery Clinic.
Patient is Fuka Nishino.
We'll be performing adhesiolysis
for traumatic adhesive ileus.
Operating surgeon, Numata.
Assistant, Kato.
-Anesthesiologist, Shimizu.
-Scrub nurse, Yamada.
Circulating nurse, Okano.
Estimated time, two hours. Let's proceed.
-Right.
-Scalpel.
And if you have any questions after
you get home, feel free to contact us.
-This way.
-Ms. Tanaka.
We were expecting you.
If you'd come this way.
CLINIC VICE-DIRECTOR
RUI KOMIYA
Hello.
We'll need to take some photos
before your consultation,
so could you remove your makeup please?
Okay.
Take your time.
GOD OF UPDATES
So, you're getting surgery
for an audition?
That's great, Ms. Tanaka.
-What?
-That's really great.
A clear goal's the best motivator.
It makes me want to help you
achieve your dream.
Can I call you Yoshiko?
Uh…
-Okay.
Tell me, first,
what area do you want to change, Yoshiko?
Don't be embarrassed.
It's not,
uh, one area I want to change.
Um, it's more like
everything?
-Everything?
-Oh, I'm sorry!
-I know that's impossible.
-No, it's not.
We have fixed pricing
on all our procedures, so no upselling.
And you'd qualify
for our first-time discount.
The model discount
varies on your media reach--
-Uh, I'm sorry, but I--
-No way.
It's your birth month, Yoshiko.
Stack a birthday discount on top,
it's like a Happy Meal.
No, that's not it. I want
the director to do the procedure.
-The director?
-Uh…
The Hand Of God.
SUCCESSOR OF THE HAND OF GOD
RIN TOHYAMA
Oh, I'm sorry.
I should have told the front desk earlier.
Mm.
But discounts don't apply
with the director.
What?
If performed by the director,
the price becomes…
And she's booked out.
I think the waiting list
is six months long for surgery.
-Six months?
-The audition will be over by then.
So, you didn't do it in the end?
Mm.
Oh, good. That was the right call.
I mean, you're already cute
as you are, you know.
It hurts worse coming from someone
who was born with good looks.
I'm so not good-looking.
I'd say I'm solidly average at best.
Oh, hey, there's another
paid drinking gig tomorrow.
Are you free, Tanaka?
I'm not in the mood for that.
My dad's been hospitalized again,
and I'm getting a lot of pressure
to drop out
and take over the family business.
I see. Your family
owns a flower shop, right?
-Mm-hmm.
-Here. Give it a try.
How many times?
If it looks like you had work done,
it defeats the purpose. Moron.
Why are you still laughing?
You know, I feel like another
tabloid exposé will destroy the agency.
In this place,
there's not a single natural beauty.
Yeah, yeah.
Your yearbook photo was the hardest one
to touch up, actually.
Anyway, what was this job
you were talking about?
It's tonight.
Do you think you can go?
No, I can't go.
I told you, I'm still in recovery, okay?
Calm down. You had a boob job.
Just wear an oversized shirt.
Come on.
I've got the Girls Collection soon.
You know how much I've been
looking forward to that opportunity.
No way. I'm not risking it.
I see. Dr. Rin
will be disappointed, though.
Oh, Dr. Rin?
Welcome.
Hey, Tanaka. That was Kanabun, wasn't it?
-Her boobs are huge.
-Wow. This party's amazing.
I literally just saw Matt.
-Uh…
-Over there. Isn't that Kotomi Hiiragi?
-What?! Where?
-There. Look!
Wow. When you're a top voice actor,
you get invited to parties like this.
Wait, Yoshiko?
-Huh?
-You're working this event?
Uh… Y… Yeah. Um…
-I'm so sorry about earlier.
-Don't worry about it.
Anyway, what a great crowd, huh?
I can't say this too loudly,
but they're all our clients.
What?
Our director won
Beauty of the Year last year,
so this is a celebration.
Cheers!
Your lips look fantastic.
Take a picture?
Oh, hi. Are you okay?
Would you like some water?
No. I'm good.
Huh? What?
The Hand of God is making her entrance.
Living in the home you tore apart
Won't take it any longer
You did everything to hurt me
So beautiful!
Rin!
Oh, she's so perfect!
I want to tell all of our clients
thank you for being here.
Each and every one of you
here tonight,
you are all my creations.
Works of art
I delicately crafted in pursuit of beauty.
Thank you, Dr. Rin.
-I love you!
-Thank you, Dr. Rin!
All of us
at the Tohyama Cosmetic Surgery Clinic
thank you for your support.
Dr. Rin!
Dr. Rin, I love you!
Now, it wouldn't be a party at all
if I just left you
without giving you a surprise, would it?
Look at that!
Wow.
A little bird told me
that all the cosmetic surgery clinics
in Tokyo are in a panic.
Wait. What is it?
Because I bought up
the entire supply of the best Botox.
-That's Botox?
-Have as many rounds as you'd like.
Until you are all content and satisfied.
Tonight, I say… enjoy yourselves!
Yay!
I want it, I want it!
Kanabun, you literally
had surgery last week.
Botox is a different story.
It'll sting a bit.
There.
Tanaka, this is sick.
It's completely whack.
Dr. Tojo, can't you hear the phone?
-Me?
-Probably just that debt collector again.
You know it's not our job
to deal with those kinds of calls.
Well, I don't think it's a doctor's job,
either, you know?
And what if it's an actual emergency, huh?
Katsushika Medical University Hospital.
I'm sorry to call so late.
This is Makihara from Nagomi Bank.
Is Dr. Numata available?
E806
VACANT
Hey, how many times do I have to tell you,
no breaks in the inpatient ward.
-What? Ow!
-Huh?
-What is it?
-I'm not your assistant.
It's Makihara
from that whatchamacallit bank.
Why don't you tell him I'm not here?
You're bothering everyone.
Oh, hello, Mr. Makihara.
This is Numata. Yes, yes, I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry to interrupt.
I know you're busy.
I'm calling about the outstanding debt
from Change the World.
-The business you co-manage.
-Oh no, listen, I… I don't co-manage it.
I don't even know why my name's on it.
The payment deadline
is at the end of the month.
-I was planning to come by your hospital--
-Oh, sorry, I have a surgery to perform!
I'll call you back later.
-What?
-We have an emergency.
Comatose at a party?
Must be alcohol poisoning.
Actually, the patient
hadn't been drinking.
The hotel sent someone over
with her belongings.
You should talk to her directly.
No alcohol…
Wait, did she get injections?
Yes. She had a few shots, and suddenly
she started drifting in and out.
You said she was at a party.
How did she get injections?
We're going to run a CT scan now.
Let's find out the source of your pain.
It might be
a little uncomfortable, but hang in there.
She's a natural beauty influencer.
Dr. Tojo is a huge fan of hers.
Yeah, he never misses her live streams.
A large abscess pressing on the silicone.
-And some findings indicate a tumor.
-What?
Silicone?
She's not a natural beauty after all.
-Huh?
-Huh.
Her yearbook photo was adorable, though.
I know, right?
The patient will be here soon.
-You know her?
-No way.
-Hey!
-Huh? Uh…
Ms. Kokubun, the pain you're feeling
is coming from an abscess
in your left breast.
It's pressing against the implant.
So we are going to need
to remove the silicone before--
-Doctor!
-Yes?
-Don't take the silicone out.
-That's your concern?
So the natural beauty thing was a lie.
That's her concern. Let's begin. Go ahead.
Okay, I'm gonna put a mask on you.
-We're starting.
-You're gonna feel drowsy.
Hm? She concealed her self-harm scars.
Checking now.
She had surgery only a week ago.
She's crazy to get Botox
so soon after surgery.
Her eyes, nose, and jaw
have all been operated on.
It's harder to find a natural part of her.
-Here.
-Right.
Let's proceed.
MOM
Mom, hi.
Seriously, why didn't you
pick up sooner? What's going on?
I'm still on shift.
I'm sorry. I have to go.
Wait! They're saying
your dad might not make it past next week.
Listen, Yoshiko.
I can't do this alone anymore.
And I can't keep the shop closed forever.
Sorry, I'm still at work, Mom.
Wait, wait!
So, does being an influencer
require you to put foreign materials
in your body while you heal?
Hm.
So, Dr. Tojo,
now that you've met her in person,
what do you think?
Not funny.
This is what you were so excited about.
Focus.
Hm, looks good.
-Irrigation.
-Ready.
Inhale.
And exhale.
Connect to your core.
Here.
Thanks.
Oh. I made your rice portion smaller
since you had champagne last night.
That's not nice.
-Okay, let's have our meal.
-Let's have our meal.
GREAT PARTY LAST NIGHT.
LET ME THANK YOU WITH DINNER?
Have you heard anything about Kanabun?
I just talked to President Kenzaki.
Kanabun's resting at the hospital.
Always double-check
who you send invitations to.
That girl,
she just had her stitches out.
My apologies.
The media can't know.
They haven't found anything out?
No.
Sales have been growing steadily
over the past month, but what concerns me
is that the revenue gap
between the Roppongi flagship
and our other locations
has widened since last year.
Plus, the revenue gap
between the director and the other doctors
is the largest it's ever been.
Does anyone have something to say?
I have one set of hands.
I only have one body.
If it's too hard
to get an appointment with us,
then we might start losing patients.
Um,
I have a suggestion.
What if we ran an ad
positioning all our doctors
as successors of the Hand of God?
And why would we do that?
The image of the chairman,
your predecessor, is still very strong,
and a lot of clients associate
Tohyama Clinic with the Hand of God.
SUCCESSOR OF THE HAND OF GOD
That's why all the bookings
are concentrated on you, Director.
The problem is…
…I think that would be
lying to our clients.
What?
It'd be strange
to have that many gods, wouldn't it?
That's right. I apologize.
Well, as it happens, we've started
looking for highly-skilled doctors,
including those from general medicine.
-Takashina.
-Yes.
Offering great skill at every scale,
big and small, that
is the value of Tohyama Clinic.
I expect everyone
to keep working to improve their skills.
In the event earnings fall,
I won't hesitate to restaff doctors.
Just remember that.
8. FUMI NUMATA
EMERGENCY/RECONSTRUCTIVE SURGERY
No, seriously, I feel a lot better.
Like a huge weight has been lifted.
Maybe it's because I was able
to sleep so well with the anesthesia.
I actually feel better
than I did before I got sick.
Well, good. I'm glad it wasn't worse.
Especially with the GC coming up.
Oh, yeah, about that…
-I thought of a cool thing to do.
-What is it?
What if we start rolling the cameras
24 hours before the event?
Like a behind-the-scenes documentary?
Exactly! Like those celebrity docs.
I can see the banner.
"Kanabun's lifelong dream comes true."
"She's joining
the Girls Collection family."
Hm?
What's wrong?
It's gone?
Gone? What's gone?
What's wrong? Kana?
What the…
Where the hell did it go?!
How dare you make a decision like that?
What is wrong with you people?!
We sincerely apologize.
The doctor said it was an emergency.
I told them
to leave the silicone in its place!
Didn't I tell you?!
-That, uh, was…
-The GC is in two weeks.
-I can't go like this!
-It's unacceptable!
It's the Girls Collection.
Do you understand? Girls Collection!
Do you idiots know how hard she's worked
to appear at the GC?!
We are truly sorry.
-Come on, Chief, stop apologizing.
-Huh?
Numata.
This is a hospital.
We removed the source of her condition.
Are you seriously willing
to risk your life for your looks?
You promised the silicone would stay in.
If we put it back in and you die,
the GC won't matter anyway.
Watch your mouth.
Who do you think you are?
Sir, please calm down.
And Dr. Numata, do watch your mouth.
Here.
I'll kill myself.
Look, let me be clear.
I had to take the silicone out
because you were in critical condition
and about to die.
If I hadn't taken it out,
you might have died.
What don't you get, you moron?
I want to die!
Huh?
Hey, stop. Kanabun, calm down!
Kanabun, easy, easy. Sit down.
SNACK BAR ITTENBARI
I think we need another.
I'm back.
So early.
-What's going on, Fumi?
-I'm not feeling well.
You're not wearing makeup.
Did you go to work like that?
Oh, my, it's embarrassing.
Leave me alone.
Hey, no! Mama was saving that for later!
Hey, the seasoning's
really good this time.
-Did you add sugar?
-I can't believe this.
Eat with us. Mr. Makihara,
could you boil up one more portion?
Sure thing.
How many bundles do you want?
Ah. I'm sorry
for calling during surgery last night.
You know what? I'm not that hungry.
Why is Nagomi Bank
boiling noodles in my house?!
This is trespassing.
Did you call the cops?
-Dad let him in.
-What?
Dad says that modern loan sharks
don't use violence anymore.
They don't want to get sued. So you're
better off making them your allies.
That's why you were having lunch together.
-Yeah.
-What an idiot!
No wonder dad racked up
200 million yen in debt!
But he doesn't seem like such a bad guy.
-Hmph.
-Here you go.
What's that?
You left work early again after
getting chewed out by your boss, right?
Oh, Takeru!
You're the only one
who really understands me.
I got in trouble today
only because I saved someone's life.
How silly is that?
I'm serious. Some folks you just
can't talk to. They're a lost cause.
-And that's what I was trying to explain--
-Do you mind?
My fave's going live in a sec.
-Your fave?
-Mm.
-Who is she, a K-pop girl?
-No, you wouldn't know her.
Tell me…
-Hey, who is it?
-You don't know her.
Try me. Who is she?
-A model.
-Mm-hmm.
A model.
-Kanabun. She's amazing.
-Kanabun?
Mm.
No, forget about her.
Stay away from that one. I'm not kidding.
-What? Kanabun?
-Mm.
Wait, the one…
-She's cute.
-With the, uh…
-Cute, huh?
-Mm.
Okay, Ms. Tanaka. We're going to be
taking your photos in the studio today.
-Right.
-Yoshiko.
Ah.
You're back.
I'm glad. I knew I'd see you again.
I requested the director.
There was a cancellation,
so I squeezed in.
Oh.
Hm.
Eyes to the camera, please.
Since I'm doing this,
I won't compromise.
I can make your eyes, nose and jaw
the way you want.
I think we should also shave the jawline
a little for overall balance.
It'll give you a delicate
and sophisticated look.
So…?
JAWLINE REDUCTION
¥1,520,000
Dr. Tohyama, whatever you say.
I'm in your hands.
I appreciate that.
But getting every surgery done
before the audition
would be too hard on your body.
So first, we'll do your eyes.
Then we'll fix your nose and jawline.
And we'll take care of your E-line.
We'll make sure those are done
in time for your audition.
It'll be okay.
Yes.
-You're really getting surgery?
-Yeah.
I need to show that kind of commitment
if I want my parents on board.
Oh, and about that drinking gig
you invited me to,
I want to do it.
I need to earn extra money. Can I join in?
I mean, isn't she an angel?
What?
-It's confidential. I can't say.
-Come on.
-Oh, she posted a story.
-What if I said it anyway?
-I could give you a hint.
-Holy crap!
What's wrong?
It says that Kanabun's dead.
What?!
WE REGRET TO ANNOUNCE
THE PASSING OF KANA KOKUBUN
Are you serious?
I'll kill myself!
Disciplinary action?
A one-month suspension to start,
and after that, you'll be transferred
to an affiliated hospital.
Wait a sec. Why am I being disciplined?
Isn't it obvious?
The patient explicitly asked
to be restored to her prior condition.
And you disregarded her request.
Isn't that right, Tojo?
And it appears that Ms. Kokubun
left a suicide note.
She wrote,
"I will never forgive Dr. Numata."
No. I mean…
She had a foreign object
lodged in her body
and she clearly was in critical condition.
Isn't it a doctor's job
to save patients like that?
Am I wrong?
Actually, if anyone's to blame,
it's the cosmetic surgeon.
Performing a breast augmentation
on a patient with a tumor
is a huge violation of medical ethics.
First of all, there were many complaints
about your conduct already.
You were taking breaks in
the inpatient ward without authorization.
And you made other staff
deal with your personal debt collectors.
Isn't that right, Tojo?
Good grief.
You should be grateful
you still have a job.
Then I'm out of here.
-What?
-Numata?
If this hospital won't support
its doctors, then I'd better quit.
Hey, uh, Numata, wait!
Her condition deteriorated
because of the silicone?
That's impossible.
Was that doctor qualified?
I mean, I wouldn't
call that woman a doctor.
She was out of her depth.
Poor Kanabun.
Sorry she had to go through that.
Oh, I'm late.
The trial ran long this morning.
-Oh, Mr. Kenzaki.
-Hi.
Hello. How far did you get?
I haven't had lunch. Mind if I eat?
Hey, Numata.
I'm sorry.
I never thought
it would turn out like that.
I should have protected you.
Don't act like my boyfriend
just because we slept together once.
I'm not interested in your sorries.
I won't go down without a fight.
Hey…
-Mr. Inoue, I need your help.
-Mm-hmm.
I will not be satisfied
until I see that quack behind bars.
If that's what you want,
I can't exactly say no, can I?
But that means
Kanabun's surgery will be exposed.
-Huh?
-What do you expect?
If this goes to court,
the whole case hinges on whether
it was necessary to remove the implant.
And the second that comes up, there'll be
questions about the other models as well.
You sure your agency wants that?
Yeah. Uh, no…
In other words,
I think the risk is too high.
And on top of that…
…the doctor may try
to shift the blame onto you,
so we need to get ahead of that.
No, wait, hold on.
Why are we the ones
who have to deal with that?
Because no one
wants to be labeled a murderer.
She'll argue the procedure
was 100% necessary to save her life.
That the blame should fall on whoever
put an implant in a breast with a tumor.
I'll get straight to the point.
Is there any way
to stop her from filing charges?
Absolutely not.
That is a right everyone's entitled to.
But, still,
we might be able
to weaken the credibility of the charges.
And for that, oh…
we'll need Mr. Takashina's help.
-Mr. Takashi!
-Whoo! Yeah!
Come on, let's dance!
Whoo!
STILL NOT OVER KANABUN.
DROP THE SURGERY TALK
KANABUN NEVER HAD PLASTIC SURGERY
PLASTIC SURGERY? WHERE?
Even the comments are fake.
Excuse me. I brought you some tea.
You can't just walk in!
So sorry.
Well, then, I'll just leave it here.
Plastic surgery, huh?
-You're switching to plastic surgery?
-Of course not, moron.
I hear it pays really well.
Might make it easier
to take care of your debt.
Listen. I'm not blood-related
to that old guy downstairs.
He's just my mother's new husband.
All right? We're total strangers.
Just a reminder,
if the transfer doesn't clear by tomorrow,
then the interest rate will be--
Shut up and get out now!
Out. Out!
The interest rate…
STILL NOT OVER KANABUN
SHE LOOKS NOTHING LIKE SHE DID
AS A KID. THERE'S PROOF
SURGERY DISASTERS OKURA
EXPOSING THE DARK SIDE AND DISASTERS
OF THE COSMETIC SURGERY INDUSTRY
No, seriously, Tanaka's voice is insane.
Hey, Tanaka, do Nastassia.
She sounds exactly like her!
Really? Do it, please.
My daughter's obsessed with this show.
Okay, could you close your eyes?
Just for a sec.
"Every last one of you,
you're a bunch of pigs."
"Greedy little piggies like you
should be happy to lick my feet."
-That sounded just like her!
-Right?
Like she was here.
She's really good.
COSMETIC SURGERY CREMATORIUM:
SURGERY DISASTERS OKURA
I BET IT'S THE T-YAMA DIRECTOR
I'VE RUN INTO HER
T-yama?
T-YAMA COSMETIC CLINIC
TOHYAMA COSMETIC SURGERY CLINIC
TOHYAMA
REBIRTH
SUCCESSOR OF THE HAND OF GOD
Tanaka,
do you have any plans right now, or…
Not really, no.
Oh.
I think you've caught the eye
of the chubby one.
He said he'd give you
this for a date.
This audition will be decided by looks.
We'll get through this.
I KNOW HOW KANABUN REALLY DIED.
CAN WE MEET IN PERSON?
Oh, wait, wait, wait. Wait a minute!
-I said no kissing, remember?
-Oh, yeah. Sorry.
Hey, can you
do the Nastassia voice though?
Come on. Please?
MOM
It's okay.
Let's trust Dr. Rin.
Excuse me, Ms. Tanaka.
Everything's ready for you, okay?
We can start.
Okay.
-This is from yesterday.
-I saw it. It's crazy!
So good-looking.
Excuse me…
Are you the one who reached out?
Oh, are you Okura?
Yeah. I'm Okura.
Nice to meet you.
Wanna sit somewhere?
Sounds good.
This is Okayu.
Oh. Ah.
Fans think Kanabun's plastic surgery
was an open secret.
Actually, every model at the agency
has had work done.
Was hers done at Tohyama Clinic?
Yeah.
They say it was handled by the director.
Is, um,
Kanabun's death connected
to Tohyama Clinic too?
Yeah? Whoa!
Well, then,
it's time to say goodbye
to your current self.
Okay.
Okay, I'm ready.
Do you trust me?
Yes.
Okay, this might sting a little.
Here we go.
-Tohyama, huh? That's a tough one.
-Why is that?
Huh. It's like the director
is basically a celebrity at this point.
Her father's famous, too,
and they advertise everywhere.
The media will ignore it
unless there's overwhelming evidence.
Well, actually, I've got some.
Before she passed away,
Ms. Kanabun had an emergency surgery
and I know the surgeon very well.
Will that surgeon
agree to talk on camera or not?
On camera?
Well, no, sorry. Um…
As a matter of fact,
Tohyama Clinic is very well-protected,
so you know.
And their lawyers are ruthless.
I heard they even hired
a former detective for crisis management.
Really?
Oh, going out, Mr. Makihara?
Going to collect from another client.
Ah.
Oh, by the way,
the prep for dinner's all done.
-Oh, thank you, as always.
-Oh, no, no.
Mr. Makihara, why don't you
just move in with us?
What?
-Okay, see you later.
-Take care.
Are you with Nagomi Bank?
Huh? Can I help you?
I would like to talk to you
about the Numata family's debt.
-Huh? What--
-In the car!
What the hell?
Do you know of any other third party
who might be willing to testify?
I don't think I do.
If the surgeon won't go on record,
we'll need multiple testimonies.
For example, someone
who was actually at the party
when she got sick.
Wait.
Yeah. She got a few shots and then
she just started drifting in and out.
Oh, you mean Ms. Tanaka.
Yes. I wanted to thank her for bringing
the patient to the ER that night.
Hey, Hina,
is Ms. Tanaka here yet?
Uh, no. Ms. Tanaka's off today.
Uh… I really need to talk to her soon.
Her next shift, when is it?
I don't know when she'll be here again.
I heard she's taking two weeks off.
-Two weeks off?
-At least.
Ah, no. Uh…
Maybe I could reach out to her directly?
There's still some swelling,
so you might be startled
when you see yourself.
But rest assured,
it went really well.
Try to stay home for the next
two weeks until the swelling goes down.
Eat well and take it easy.
Once you get through that,
you'll become a whole new person,
Ms. Tanaka.
Recovery time
is what's necessary
for a chrysalis to break out of its cocoon
and transform into a butterfly.
OUR APPROACH TO RECOVERY TIME
It might feel lonely, frightening even,
to stay still in a dark cocoon.
But when you want to fly
with beautiful wings,
it's the price to pay.
Hang in there.
You'll be okay.
Oh, and I forgot to mention,
try not to cry if you can,
or the swelling takes longer to heal.
I wish you'd said so earlier.
Mm.
Sup? I'm back.
What's going on?
Fumi,
why did you quit the hospital?
Huh?
I, uh… That hospital's so toxic.
You wouldn't believe all the drama there.
Wait. How do you know?
Ah, she's back.
Okay, take a seat.
-Huh? Why? I've got things to do.
-I said sit down!
Go.
Go!
There are gonna be consequences
if you quit working as a doctor.
Huh?
Your salary is collateral on your debt.
Of course it is. Did you think this
snack bar was gonna cover 200 million yen?
I quit the hospital, but that doesn't mean
I quit being a doctor, okay?
Yeah, sure. But how are you
gonna get a job after that scandal?
What scandal?
Huh?
God, you're clueless.
What does it say?
#FUMI_NUMATA #PSYCHO_DOCTOR
#MEDICAL_LICENSE_REVOKED
What? What is this?
-Yeah, hello?
-Hey, is everything okay over there?
The hospital is being swarmed
by the media.
How is it
my personal information is out there?
I've got no idea either.
Hey, listen.
The chief wants to talk again.
They'll want you
to give an official explanation.
Hello? Numata? You there?
So, what do I do?
Selling the house
would only clear 50 million yen, right?
Hold on, Mr. Makihara.
We'll figure it out. We will.
We'll keep this bar going
and pay you back little by little.
Just don't take the house.
Please. I beg you!
Listen, my son, is still in junior high.
Just, please, give…
Just until he starts high school.
That's all I'm asking. Okay?
Please. I beg you.
Please. Until high school. That's all.
Mr. Makihara.
Th… This is all my fault.
I made bad investments.
I'm such an idiot!
I'll work as hard as I have to work.
I beg you!
Mr. Makihara, please.
Takeru.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Even if you beg, it doesn't change
the fact that you owe me money!
I just need one more week.
Huh?
Takeru.
Takeru, that's enough.
I'm sorry.
So, you're gonna get
200 million yen in a week?
No, of course I won't.
But that scandal is based on lies.
I'll set the record straight
and go back to work.
As long as I'm working as a doctor,
we're good, right?
Huh.
That works for me.
In one week then.
Takeru. It's okay.
I'm sorry.
Ms. Tanaka? Excuse me?
Excuse-- Oh.
Who is it?
I'm Numata. We met
at Katsushika University Hospital.
Um, I'm the one
who operated on Ms. Kanabun.
What do you want?
I need your help with something.
If you could give me a minute--
Oh boy.
I can't be associated
with a psycho doctor.
-Just leave me alone.
-I just need a minute!
Ms. Tanaka.
I promise it won't take long at all.
And now you've moved on to a new phase
involving debt evasion or something.
Honestly, with so much heat,
even my site can't help you on this one.
All right.
I'll go ahead
and share everything I know on camera.
I'll talk about Kanabun's surgery
in details. Does that change things?
-I'm sorry.
-Why?
I mean, like I told you already,
Tohyama's bad news.
These people will seriously
stop at nothing.
What?
So Tohyama is behind the scandal?
I think it's very likely.
That's… That's too far.
I mean, a company that runs commercials
on TV wouldn't act like a bunch of yakuza.
That's the plastic surgery industry
for you.
Since reviews have an effect on sales,
they get rid of negative publicity
by any means necessary.
Business owners, and celebrities…
They have close ties
with influential people.
So their misdeeds are covered up,
and there are a lot of citizens
who are frustrated.
Which is why my site is so successful.
ARE YOU SATISFIED WITH WHO YOU ARE NOW?
So today we're at the top-rated
plastic surgery clinic,
Tohyama Cosmetic Surgery Clinic.
-Isn't it exciting?
-Thanks.
-Thank you.
-We're finally here.
-This is amazing.
-Yeah.
Okay, without further ado, here they are.
Oh, wonderful!
-Wow! Incredible. This is the director.
-Wow!
-Thanks for having us.
-Hello.
Wow, the Hand of God
has an intense aura, doesn't she?
What a treat.
I know this is a weird question to ask,
but how much would it cost
to get a facelift like yours?
-That's rude!
-Oh, I'm so sorry.
I actually haven't had
any work done myself yet.
-Really?
This is unadulterated?
"Unadulterated?"
I don't think that's how it's called.
-Oh.
-You're so perfect.
Hey--
Do you have an appointment?
I need to talk to you.
-Can I help you?
-What's going on?
You know why I'm here.
This is about Ms. Kanabun.
We can schedule you
for a consultation later?
-I just want to have a word.
-Ma'am, you need to stop.
And you call yourself a doctor? Huh?
How can you live with yourself
after a surgery like that?!
-Stop, now!
-Hey!
What kind of beauty is that? Screw you!
It was you. You killed that girl!
-This way.
-Go to hell!
-Come on.
-Let go of me!
-Hey, you!
Hey!
Stop it! Enough!
Ha. God, that went exactly as expected.
Actually, better than expected.
Now you don't have to worry
about any allegations.
You don't know her.
I don't think she'll give up that easily.
-We need to find a way to stop that girl.
-It's already taken care of.
The university hospital just put out a
statement acknowledging the medical error.
Whatever she says now,
nobody's gonna believe her.
Ah, by the way,
Mr. Takashina mentioned
something interesting.
Do you remember that list
of top doctors we wanted to recruit?
Well, there is someone.
Here, look at this.
It's that psycho doctor.
FUMI NUMATA
GRADE A
She's got the highest technical score.
She's pretty good.
KITA-AZABU POLICE STATION
Mm.
Oh yeah. Yeah, yeah.
Yeah. It was so much quicker
than the other ones.
TOHYAMA
SUCCESSOR OF THE HAND OF GOD
How would you like to work
at our cosmetic clinic?
Huh? What are you saying?
Don't take this the wrong way, Fumi,
but I can guarantee you more than three
times your university hospital salary.
Are you trying to buy my silence?
How dirty are you?
Dirty?
Nothing dirty about this.
I'm simply telling you, you would have
a nice, but fair salary, Doctor.
Why would I ever
want to work in cosmetic surgery?
We could take care of your debt as well.
Two hundred million yen, wasn't it?
I don't think it's such a bad deal.
You can continue to practice medicine
like you always have.
And you get to rescue your dear family.
You're a bit curious.
I'm right, aren't I?
Hm.
I won't forgive you.
-Sorry?
-I'll say it again.
I… will never forgive you.
I couldn't care less
if you forgive me or not.
I care about one thing.
I don't want the clinic's reputation
to be tarnished.
Well, then,
I'll wait for you at the clinic.
Hey!
Wait! Hey, go to hell!
Okay?!
Screw you!
Go to hell!
Shit!